const QuizeData=[
          {cname:'Angular',
          quizes:[
            {cname:'Quiz 1',
             times:30,questions:[
              {
                question:'one equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,6],
                correct:0
              },
              {
                question:'Four equal to',
                answers:[1,4,5,6],
                correct:1
              },
              {
                question:'Eighty equal to',
                answers:[1,24,80,6],
                correct:2
              },
              {
                question:'Sixty equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,60],
                correct:3
              }
             ]
            },
            {cname:'Quiz 2',
             times:30,questions:[
              {
                question:'two equal to',
                answers:[1,2,5,6],
                correct:1
              },
              {
                question:'Three equal to',
                answers:[1,24,3,6],
                correct:2
              },
              {
                question:'six equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,6],
                correct:3
              },
              {
                question:'seven equal to',
                answers:[1,24,7,6],
                correct:2
              }
             ]
            }
          ]},
          {cname:'React',quizes:[
            {cname:'Quiz 1',
             times:30,questions:[
              {
                question:'one equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,6],
                correct:0
              },
              {
                question:'Four equal to',
                answers:[1,4,5,6],
                correct:1
              },
              {
                question:'Eighty equal to',
                answers:[1,24,80,6],
                correct:2
              },
              {
                question:'Sixty equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,60],
                correct:3
              }
             ]
            },
            {cname:'Quiz 2',
             times:30,questions:[
              {
                question:'two equal to',
                answers:[1,2,5,6],
                correct:1
              },
              {
                question:'Three equal to',
                answers:[1,24,3,6],
                correct:2
              },
              {
                question:'six equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,6],
                correct:3
              },
              {
                question:'seven equal to',
                answers:[1,24,7,6],
                correct:2
              }
             ]
            }
          ]},
          {cname:'C++',quizes:[
            {cname:'Quiz 1',
             times:30,questions:[
              {
                question:'one equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,6],
                correct:0
              },
              {
                question:'Four equal to',
                answers:[1,4,5,6],
                correct:1
              },
              {
                question:'Eighty equal to',
                answers:[1,24,80,6],
                correct:2
              },
              {
                question:'Sixty equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,60],
                correct:3
              }
             ]
            },
            {cname:'Quiz 2',
             times:30,questions:[
              {
                question:'two equal to',
                answers:[1,2,5,6],
                correct:1
              },
              {
                question:'Three equal to',
                answers:[1,24,3,6],
                correct:2
              },
              {
                question:'six equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,6],
                correct:3
              },
              {
                question:'seven equal to',
                answers:[1,24,7,6],
                correct:2
              }
             ]
            }
          ]},
          {cname:'JavaScript',quizes:[
            {cname:'Quiz 1',
             times:30,questions:[
              {
                question:'one equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,6],
                correct:0
              },
              {
                question:'Four equal to',
                answers:[1,4,5,6],
                correct:1
              },
              {
                question:'Eighty equal to',
                answers:[1,24,80,6],
                correct:2
              },
              {
                question:'Sixty equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,60],
                correct:3
              }
             ]
            },
            {cname:'Quiz 2',
             times:30,questions:[
              {
                question:'two equal to',
                answers:[1,2,5,6],
                correct:1
              },
              {
                question:'Three equal to',
                answers:[1,24,3,6],
                correct:2
              },
              {
                question:'six equal to',
                answers:[1,24,5,6],
                correct:3
              },
              {
                question:'seven equal to',
                answers:[1,24,7,6],
                correct:2
              }
             ]
            }
          ]}
]
export default QuizeData;